# Otun Stephen Gbenga

12, Opeyemi Street, Eleta, Ibadan,
Oyo State, Nigeria.
Stephenotun26@gmail.com
08130698806, 08154956803

# Personal profile

A hard-working, dependable and committed individual who is able to work well as part of a team as well as under own initiative. A proactive teacher and researcher with six years plus experience in teaching and administrative sectors. Has excellent communication skills and is able to liaise with colleagues and customers in a professional manner. Trust worthy and reliable and able to follow instructions to maintain a high work output with great accuracy and efficiency.

#### Core skills

Presentation of ideas convincingly through well-constructed, systematic arguments

Generation of ideas and solutions to problems

The ability to prioritise work and meet deadlines

The capacity to identify, absorb and sift complex information

Team working

Resource planning

# **Employment History**

English Language teacher: Misty Gee Model College, Ile Ife, Osun state. 2018- June 2019

Sales representative at Maxi Pride Concepts, Ile Ife, Osun state. 2015 to October 2017

English Language teacher: Akahi tutors, Deligent tutors, 2013- November 2014

Class teacher: Rare Gem Model College, Ile Ife, Osun state. 2013- February 2014

## **Education**

Theological education, Christ Apostolic Church, Seminary, Ibadan, 2019 till present.

Masters of Arts, (PhD grade) Philosophy. University of Ibadan, November 2016

Bachelor of Arts, (2nd class upper division) Philosophy, University of Ibadan, 2013

### **Core qualifications**

Excellent organizational skills

Excellent computer skills (Microsoft office, Word, outlook, and using the internet)

Effective written and verbal communication skills

Knowledge of Church Latin and New Testament Greek.

### Reference

Iyaji Joseph Akahi,

Education consultant, Akahi tutors.

08038644328.